The origin of internal asymmetry, at the level of this node
内部の非対称性の起源は、このエンゼンス結節のレベルで、
of Hensen,
エンゼンス結節では、
we observe that there are small cilia,
小さな繊毛があることがわかります。
and these small cilia, as I told you, when we observe them,
そして、これらの小さな繊毛は、私が言ったように、観察すると、
they don't make a movement like this, but a rotatory movement.
このように動くのではなく、回転運動をします。
And they accelerate when they are higher than their base relative to the ground.
そして、それらは地面に対する基部よりも高い位置にあると加速します。
And they bring small molecules,
そして、それらは小さな分子を運びます。
which come from the roof, we are in our cord, inside.
それは屋根から来て、私たちは私たちのコードの中にいます。
inside.
内部に。
There, that's the fulcrum, okay?
そこが支点です、いいですか？
You see, that's the fixed point.
ほら、それが固定点です。
And here, we enter here.
そして、ここ、ここに入ります。
It's a big mess.
それは大混乱です。
And above, there are cilia.
そして、その上には繊毛があります。
And in fact, above, you can imagine, there are...
そして実際、その上には、想像してみてください、
Really, that's the image they describe.
本当に、それが彼らが説明するイメージです。
These are called small vesicles that fall,
それは小さな小胞と呼ばれ、そこに落ちて、
there, and which are brought to concentrate towards one side.
そして、それらは片側に集中するように運ばれます。
And these small vesicles collide, if
そして、これらの小さな小胞は、もしあなたが望むなら、過剰によって衝突し、
you will, by the excess, and release many morphogens
そして、たくさんのモルフォゲンを下の地面に放出します。
on the ground, underneath.
下の地面に。
You have genes that are activation genes.
活性化遺伝子と呼ばれる遺伝子があります。
they activate even more
それらはさらに活性化します。
or inhibition genes
または抑制遺伝子。
there you go
ほら。
I'm summarizing genetics for you
遺伝学を要約します。
and that's what will create
そして、それが非対称性の構造を作り出すものです。
in fact these asymmetry structures
実際、これらの非対称性の構造が、
which later will make the heart
後で心臓が左に発達し、
develop on the left
心臓が左に発達し、
that the liver will develop
肝臓が右に発達し、
more to the right
より右に発達し、
that the brain, that all these things
脳やこれらすべての内部のものが、
internally will be
内部のものが、
asymmetrical in the center
中心で非対称になります。
we don't have
私たちは持っていません。
We have a symmetry, we have a functional asymmetry that will
私たちは対称性を持っています。私たちは機能的な非対称性を持っており、それが最終的に動きを与えます。
give us movements in the long run.
最終的に動きを与えます。
All of this will organize up to the cerebral connections, etc.
これらすべては、脳の接続などに至るまで組織化されます。
It will go very deep, but this is the starting point of asymmetry.
それは非常に深く進みますが、それが非対称性の出発点です。
The nodal flow, that's it.
節の動き、それがこれです。
It is this small movement here of the cilia that causes this nodal fluid
この小さな動き、白鳥の動きが、この節の液体を動かし、
to move,
節の液体を動かし、
to concentrate vesicles more on one side than the other.
小胞を片側に集中させ、もう一方には集中させないようにします。
which are of epiblastic origin, from the roof of the epiblast.
これらは上胚葉の屋根、上胚葉由来のものです。
That's where this whole cascade will happen, if you will,
ここに、もしあなたが望むなら、このカスケード全体が起こるでしょう。
on the left and right, with this concentration on the right,
左右のレベルで、右側にこの集中があり、
which will give cascades with the sonic hedgehog, the fibro,
ソネティックエッジ、線維芽細胞、
which are important genes that will intervene,
これらは介入する重要な遺伝子であり、
up to the pituitary, which will be pituitary genes, if you will,
もしあなたが望むなら、下垂体遺伝子であるトラックまで、
which will be important later.
これらは後で重要になります。
for the creation of new structures, new proteins,
新しい構造、新しいタンパク質、
and asymmetry, organization of the embryo.
そして非対称性、胚の組織化のために。
So it's already happening there.
だからそれはすでにそこで行われています。
So this axis is a center of organization.
したがって、この軸は組織化の中心です。
Epithelial cells, bottle cells and mesenchymal cells
上皮細胞、ボトル細胞、間葉系細胞
which will form the mesoderm.
これらが中胚葉を形成します。
So there is extra-embryonic mesoderm, intra-embryonic mesoderm,
胚体外中胚葉、胚体内中胚葉がありますが、
but it is mainly the intra-embryonic.
しかし、それは主に胚体内中胚葉です。
It is essentially derived from the epithelial.
それは本質的に上皮に由来します。
That's why at the beginning, it's electricity that first
だからこそ、最初は電気が流体を誘発し、流体を組織化し、そして流体が物質を組織化するのです。
induces the fluid, which organizes the fluid, and the fluid which organizes matter.
流体を誘発し、流体を組織化し、そして流体が物質を組織化するのです。
And that's why it's important, because in our osteopathic reflection, in our work, we
そして、それが重要なのは、私たちのオステオパシーの考察、私たちの仕事において、私たちは
work with our mental image.
私たちは心のイメージで作業します。
So what is my mental representation, because it is that which the
だから、私の心の表現は何ですか、なぜならそれは体が使うものだからです。
body will use, whether you recognize it or not.
体が使うものだからです、あなたがそれを認識するかしないかにかかわらず。